National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Case Files, 1988-2006, Undated; nam_apap298-1; 12.55 cubic ft.
  - Adults, 1988-2006, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1; 9 cubic ft.
    - Cave, Alfonso (FL), 1993; nam_apap298-1.1_211 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Cazaves, Jose Lupercio (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_212 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Ceja, Jose J. (AZ), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_213 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Chaffee, Jonathan (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_214 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Chambers, James W. (MO), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_215 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Chambers, Karl S. (PA), 1992; nam_apap298-1.1_216 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Chambers, Tony (TX), 1994; 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_217 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Chandler, Oba (FL), 1994; nam_apap298-1.1_218 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Chandler, David R. (AL), 1994; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_219 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Chaney, Anthony Lee (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_220 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Chaney, Larry (FED), 2002; nam_apap298-1.1_221 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Chappell, William Wesley (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_222 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Charping, James M. (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_223 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Cheatham, Charles L. (OK), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_224 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Chester, Frank (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_225 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Chichester, Carl (VA), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_226 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Christeson, Mark A. (MO), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_227 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Christy, Lawrence (PA), 1992; nam_apap298-1.1_228 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Clark, Andrew Bert (AL), 1994; nam_apap298-1.1_229 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Clark, Douglas (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_230 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Clark, Herman Robert Jr. (TX) Executed December 6, 1994, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_231 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Clark, Jack (TX), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_232 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Clark, James Lee (TX), 1994; nam_apap298-1.1_233 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Clark, Joseph L. (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_234 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Clark, Richard Dean (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_235 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Clark, Ronald (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_236 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Clark, William John (CA), 1993; nam_apap298-1.1_237 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Clayton, Robert (OK), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_238 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Clemons, Reginald (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_239 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Coble, Billie (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_240 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Cockrun, Johnny (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_241 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Coddington, Herbert (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_242 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Code, Nathaniel (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_243 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Coe, Robert (TN), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_244 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Coffman, Cynthia (CA), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_245 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Coldwell, Daniel (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_246 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Colella, Paul Richard (TX), 1992; nam_apap298-1.1_247 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Coleman, Alton (OH), 2002; nam_apap298-1.1_248 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Coleman, Clydell (TX), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_249 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Coleman, Russell (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_250 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Collins, Kenneth (MD), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_251 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Collins, Scott (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_252 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Colvin, Eugene S. (MD), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_253 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Colvin-El, Eugene (MD), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_254 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Comeaux, Adam (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_255 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Comer, Robert (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_256 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Conforti, Michael (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_257 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Conner, Kevin (IN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_258 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Conklin, Robert (GA), 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_259 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Cook, Daniel W. (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_260 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Cook, Derrick (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_261 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Cook, Kerry (TX), 1991; nam_apap298-1.1_262 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Cook, Robert (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_263 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Cooks, Cornel (OK), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_264 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Cooper, Carl (DC) [1 of 2], 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_265 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Cooper, Carl (DC) [2 of 2], 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_266 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Cooper, Gene Tony (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_267 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Cooper, Kevin (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_268 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Cooper, Richard M. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_269 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Copeland, Faye (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_270 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Copeland, James (LA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_271 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Corcoran, Joseph (IN), 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_272 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Cordova, Jorge (TX), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_273 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Corley, Edward Eldon (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_274 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correll, Jerry W. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_275 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Corwin, Daniel L. (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_276 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Coulter, Roger (AR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_277 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Cousan, Donald (LA), 1994; nam_apap298-1.1_278 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Cox, Donna (NC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_279 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Cox, Michael (AR), 1993; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_280 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Cox, Tiequon (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_281 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Crane, Alvin Wayne (TX), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_282 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Crawford, Charles (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_283 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Crew, Mark, (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_284 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Crews, Paul David (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_285 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Crews, William (IL), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_286 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Cross, Charles (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_287 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Cruse, William (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_288 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Cruz, Javier G. (TX), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_289 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Cruz, Rolando (IL), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_290 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Cudjo, Armenia (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_291 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Cummings, Raynard (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_292 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Cunningham, AL (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_293 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Cunningham, Clinton (OR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_294 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Curl, Robert Zane (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_295 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - D'Amato, Joseph C. (PA), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_296 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Dalton, Kerry Lyn (CA), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_297 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Daniels, Henry "Butch" (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_298 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Daniels, Jackson (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_299 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Daniels, Michael (IN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_300 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Danks, Joseph (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_301 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Davie, Roderick (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_302 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Davis, Allen (FL), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_303 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Davis, Don (AR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_304 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Davis, Gary (CO), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_305 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Davis, Girvies L. (IL) Executed May 7, 1995, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_306 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Davis, Gregory (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_307 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Davis, James (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_308 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Davis, Jimmy (AL), 1994; nam_apap298-1.1_309 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Davis, Kenneth (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_310 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Davis, Ralph (MO), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_311 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Davis, Richard (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_312 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Davis, Stanley (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_313 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Davis, Thomas (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_314 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Davis, William (TX), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_315 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Dawson, David (DE), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_316 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - DeBlanc, David (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_317 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - DeBruce, Derrick (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_318 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Deer, Ronald (CA), 1991; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_319 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - DeHoyos, Richard (CA), 1993; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_320 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - De La Cruz, Jose (TX), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_321 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Delk, Monty (TX), 2002; nam_apap298-1.1_322 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - DeLong, Wayne (VA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_323 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Dement, Ronnie (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_324 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Demps, Bennie (FL), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_325 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Dennis, Jimmy (PA), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_326 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Depew, Rhett (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_327 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - DePriest, Timothy (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_328 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Deruise, Clifford (LA), 1996; nam_apap298-1.1_329 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Detrich, David Scott (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_330 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Diaz, Angel (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_331 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Diaz, Robert (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_332 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Dickens, Gregory Scott (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_333 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Dickerson, Frederick (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_334 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Dickey, Colin (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_335 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Dillbeck, Donald (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_336 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Dillingham, Jeffrey (TX), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_337 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Djerf, Richard Kenneth (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_338 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Dobbs, Wiley (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_339 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Dodd, Westly Allan (WA), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_340 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Doerr, Eugene (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_341 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Donald, Richard (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_342 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Douglas, Fred B. (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_343 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Down, Ernest (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_344 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Dowthitt, Dennis (TX), 1998; 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_345 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Draughon, Martin (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_346 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Drayton, Leroy J. (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_347 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Drew, Robert (TX) Executed August 22, 1994, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_348 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Drinkard, Richard (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_349 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Dubois, Johnile L. (VA) August 31, 1998, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_350 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Duckett, James A. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_351 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Dudley, Marion Butler (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_352 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Duest, Llyod (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_353 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Dueffey, Steven (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_354 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Dunkle,Jon (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_355 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Dunn, Henry (TX), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_356 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Dunn, Kenneth (TX), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_357 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Duren, David (AL), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_358 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Duvall, John (OK), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_359 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Dyer, Alfred (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_360 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Earhart, James (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_361 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Earp, Ricky Lee (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_362 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Earvin, Harvey (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_363 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Eaton, Dennis N. (VA), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_364 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Eaton, Winthrop (LA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_365 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Echols, Damien (AR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_366 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Eddmonos, Durlyn (IL), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_367 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Edelbacher, Peter (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_368 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Edwards, Thomas Francis (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_369 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Eldridge, Coerald Cornellus (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_370 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Elkins, Michael E. (SC) Executed June 12, 1997, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_371 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Elledge, William (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_372 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Elliott, John Williams (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_373 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Elliot, Joseph (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_374 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Elmore, Edward L. (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_375 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Enmund, Earl (FL), 2002; nam_apap298-1.1_376 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Epperson, Roger D. (KY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_377 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Ervin, Thomas (MO), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_378 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Esparza, Gregory (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_379 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Espinoza, Antonio (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_380 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Etheridge, Gary (TX), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_381 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Evans, David L. (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_382 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Evans, Vernon Lee (MD), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_383 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Fahy, Henry (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_384 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Farina, Anthony (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_385 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Farley, Richard (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_386 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Farr, Victor M. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_387 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Farris, Troy (TX), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_388 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Fauber, Curtis Lynn (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_389 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Faulder, Stanley (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_390 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Faulkner, Arthur (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_391 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Felder Jr., Sammig (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_392 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Felker, Ellis (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_393 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Ferguson, Cornelius (DE), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_394 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Ferrell, Dallas (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_395 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Fields, Steve (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_396 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Fierro, Cesar (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_397 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Fierro, David Ray (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_398 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Fisher, David Lee (VA), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_399 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Fisher, James (OK), 1992; nam_apap298-1.1_400 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Fisher, Robert (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_401 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Fisher, Willie (NC), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_402 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Fleenor, D.H (IN), 1999; 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_403 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Fleming, Son (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_404 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Flores, Miguel Angel (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_405 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Flowers, Wendell (NC), 1999; 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_406 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Fluke, Ronald (OK), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_407 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Foley, Robert (KY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_408 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Ford, Alvin B. (FL), 2004; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_409 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Ford, Glen (LA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_410 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Ford, Kenneth (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_411 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Ford, Pernell (AL), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_412 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Ford, Priscilla (NV), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_413 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Foster, Charles K. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_414 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Foster, Charles (OK), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_415 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Foster, Emitt (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_416 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Foster, Lafonda (KY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_417 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Foster, Richard (TX), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_418 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Fotopoulos, Konstantinos (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_419 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Fowler, Mark (OK), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_420 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Fox, Billy-Ray, 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_421 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Frank, Leo (GA), 1996; nam_apap298-1.1_422 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Frank, Theodore (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_423 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Freeman, David (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_424 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Fretwell, Bobby (AR), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_425 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Frey, Roderick (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_426 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Frierson, Lavell (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_427 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Fry, Anthony (VA), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_428 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Fuller, Aaron (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_429 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Fuller, Throne (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_430 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Fulminante. Oreste (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_431 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Gall, William Eugene (KY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_432 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Gallamore, Samuel Clark (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_433 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Gallego, Gerald (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_434 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Garceau, Robert Frederick (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_435 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Garcia, Fernando (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_436 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Garcia, Guineuere (IL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_437 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Garcia, Gustavo (TX), 1991; nam_apap298-1.1_438 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Garcia, Hector Torres (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_439 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Garcia, Randy Eugene (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_440 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Gardner, David (TX), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_441 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Gardner, Mark (AR), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_442 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Garner, William Lee (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_443 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Gay, Kenneth (CA), 1993; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_444 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Gay, Yvette (NC), 1991; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_445 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Gentry, Kenneth (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_446 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Giarratano, Joseph (VA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_447 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Gibbs, David (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_448 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Gibson, Ronald (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_449 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Gilbert, Larry (SC), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_450 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Gilliam, Burley (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_451 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Gilliam, Jr., Tyrone (MD), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_452 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Gilies, Jesse (AZ), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_453 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Gladney, George Nathaniel Jr. (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_454 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Gleaton, J.D (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_455 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Glen, Robert (TN), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_456 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Glock, Robert (FL), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_457 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Goff, David Lee (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_458 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Goins, Christopher (VA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_459 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Gollehon, William (MT), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_460 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Gonzales, Jesse (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_461 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Goodman, Spencer (TX), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_462 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Goodwin, Alvin (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_463 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Gorby, Thomas (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_464 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Gordon, Patrick (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_465 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Gore, David A. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_466 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Gosch, Lesley Lee (TX), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_467 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Goss, Cornelius Alan (TX), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_468 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Goynes, Theodore (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_469 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Graham, Andre (VA), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_470 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Graham, Harrison (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_471 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Grandison, Anthony (MD), 1994; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_472 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Gray, Mario (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_473 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Gray, Marlin (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_474 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Gray, Ronald (Military), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_475 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Green, Alphonso (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_476 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Green, Anthony (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_477 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Green, Harvey (NC), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_478 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Green, Norman (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_479 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Green, Ricky (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_480 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Greene, Beau John (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_481 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Greene, Jack (AR), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_482 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Gregory, Wilson (KY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_483 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Gretzler, Douglas (AZ), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_484 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Gribble, Lane (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_485 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Gribble, Timothy (TX), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_486 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Griffin, Donald (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_487 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Griffin, Larry (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_488 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Griffin, Michael (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_489 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Griffin, Milton (MO), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_490 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Griffin, Rodney (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_491 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Groseclose, Bill (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_492 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Grossman, Martin (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_493 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Guerra, Jose Francisco (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_494 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Guerra, Ricardo Aldape (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_495 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Gulbrandson, David (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_496 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Gunsby, Donald (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_497 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Gutierrez, Isaac (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_498 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Gutierrez, Joe Angel (TX), 1994; nam_apap298-1.1_499 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Guy, Joe (TX) Stay Granted June 28, 2000, 1994; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_500 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Hasg, Ranoy (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_501 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Hackett, Richard D. (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_502 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Hafdahl, Randall (TX), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_503 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Haight, Rany (KY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_504 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Haley, Kevin (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_505 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Haliburton, Jerry (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_506 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Hall, Dennis (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_507 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Hall, Freddie Lee (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_508 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Hall, Orlando C. (AK), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_509 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Hall, Steven Wayne (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_510 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Hallford, Phillip (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_511 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Hameen, Abdullah T. (OK), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_512 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Hamilton, Bernard (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_513 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Hamilton, Billy Ray (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_514 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Hamilton, Marcus (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_515 (Box 4, Folder 101)